Owen Spicer

During my five years in the service industry I have developed many useful skills to guarantee customer/vendor satisfaction . These skills helped me maintain a 100% positive customer feedback via Service Titan while Although I have enjoyed my time in this industry, my goal is to get into the IT field by developing myself into an asset by learning in demand technologies.

4487 Lynn Forest Dr Gainesville, VA 20155 (703) 344-4396 Christopherowenspicer@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Life Time Athletic, Gainseville VA — Facility Operations Supervisor

March 2022 - Present

Ensure the functionality and cleanliness of the 130,000 square foot resort. Responsible for scheduling and overseeing 20+ employees and guaranteeing team member efficiency, training requirements, accomplishments and disciplinary action. Performed closing procedures. Manage shipments and inventory analysis. Prepared business for full operation for the following day.

Bowman's Heating, Cooling & Electrical, Sterling VA — HVAC Installer

October 2020 - October 2021

Installed and serviced various home and commercial HVAC, plumbing, electrical systems and appliances. Responsible for installation, inventory and reviewing scope of work, warranties and closing contracts.

Pin Oak Tree Services, Centreville VA — Climber & Machine Operator

May 2019 - Present

Performed tree removal, storm damage evaluation, educating clients on arboriculture preservation and maintenance. Responsible for administrative duties such as scheduling and invoice processing.

CLS Services, Gainesville VA — Window & Door Installer

June 2014 - Present

Performed the installation of premium windows and doors, evaluating structural integrity at time of removal. Responsible for inventory and job site clean up.

BestBuy, Gainesville VA — Sales Associate

March 2016 - August 2017

Informed the customers on the latest technology in all departments. Responsible for forwarding warranty information and financing options to clients. As well as downstocking and SHRINK management.

EDUCATION

West Virginia University, Morgantown, WV

August 2018 - March 2020

Obtained 64 credits, due the Covid 19 Pandemic I have delayed my education.

SKILLS

Programming language proficiency (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, some knowledge in SQL & Python)

Versitalie with different OS

Advanced knowledge with computer maintenance & hardware

Inventory Analysis

Sending & recieving shipments

Ability to work independently

Training

LANGUAGES

English and Intermediate Spanish

CERTIFICATIONS

HVAC Technician Certification -EPA Clean Air Section 608

40-Hour BestBuy Sales Floor Training